<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<level width="640" height="480" lives="1" goal="100">
	<motivation>
		This was for the "orientation challenged".
		This is based on level tuanlevel_four, where the two skaters
		are seemingly parallel. But the orientationally challenged will think
		that skaters are going east by default, and not necessarily that going east
		is really a function of the skaters behavior to go left (oriented with respect to 
		direction skater is chasing).

		So, rather than having a level mirrored across the y-axis, y=0, we have one
		mirrored across the the line y=x. This is the inverse. Players should now observe
		that both skaters are going in the same spiral, and that this spiral is really
		the same spiral as the other skater, just rotated 180 degrees (but not flipped!)
	</motivation>
	<problem>
		Again, both skaters will simultaneously spiral and get stuck. 

		Since the player already experienced a similar map, the time on this map has been increased
		for each skater. Plus, its easier to traverse back and forth between the two
		skaters by design of the map.

		But it's fine the level got easier. The players will feel they got much better, 
		and think they are so good for solving it so fast. Indeed, they are learning along the way, though.
	</problem>
	<solution>
		Same strategies as level four
	</solution>
	<progression>
		1) Level can be preceded by level that introduces player to strategy of using
		zamboni to "block" the skaters movement, forcing them to go in a certain direction.
		posibly, skater head to pitfall, and the only way to save them is by blocking them and 
		redirect them
		2) I toned the level to 17 seconds per skater. If this was increased to 20 seconds,
		the difficulty is a significantly harder
	</progression>
	<popup mainImg="skatersStuckPop" tip="BEGINNER_TIPS_INDEX"/>
	<zamboni x="504" y="160" />
	<skater x="40" y="40" toX="144" toY="120">
		<start>1</start>
		<time>21</time>
	</skater>
	<skater x="500" y="500" toX="432" toY="376">
		<start>1</start>
		<time>21</time>
	</skater>
</level>